RG 005:036, Office of the Governor: Ella Grasso (1975-1980)
Connecticut State Library
- Part VII Supplementary Files, 1971-1980
  - Speeches (Box 752)
    - Nova Scotia, 1977 June 24 (Box 754)
    - National Conference on Health Care Costs, 1977 June 27 (Box 754)
    - Conference on Service for Deaf-Blind Persons (in file only), 1977 July 8 (Box 754)
    - Earl of Carnarvon Luncheon (King Tut’s Neighbor), 1977 July 22 (Box 754)
    - 40th Anniversary on National Apprentice-ship Program, 1977 August 1 (Box 754)
    - Swearing in Ceremony of the State Board of Higher Education, 1977 August 2 (Box 754)
    - Christening Replica of First Submarine, Turtle (in file only), 1977 August 20 (Box 754)
    - Swearing-in of Weinberg as Director, SBA Region 1, Boston (in file only), 1977 September 14 (Box 754)
    - Dedication of Storm Warning Radar (in file only), 1977 September 15 (Box 754)
    - U.S. Savings Bond, 1977 September 15 (Box 754)
    - Greater Hartford and Greater New Haven Federal Executives Association, 1977 September 15 (Box 754)
    - Northeast Associated Press News Executions, Southbury, 1977 September 16 (Box 754)
    - Armstrong State College - Women, 1977 September 17 (Box 754)
    - Eastern States Expo Luncheon, 1977 September 21 (Box 754)
    - Organization Meeting of Urban Action Program, 1977 September 21 (Box 754)
    - Michigan Home Economics Association, 1977 September 23 (Box 754)
    - Concepts 77, 1977 October 12 (Box 754)
    - Bristol Association for the Retarded, 1977 October 12 (Box 754)
    - Board of Protection and Advocacy for the Handicapped, 1977 October 12 (Box 754)
    - Glastonbury Democratic Town Committee, 1977 October 12 (Box 754)
    - Dedication of Auditorium - Gymnasium Complex at Mystic Oral School, 1977 October 13 (Box 754)
    - Opening of Black Expo in New Haven, 1977 October 13 (Box 754)
    - Graduation Board for State Academic Awards, 1977 October 13 (Box 754)
    - Opening Ceremonies for Route 7, 1977 October 13 (Box 754)
    - Elderly Housing Dedication, Bellwoods Court, East Hampton, 1977 October 16 (Box 754)
    - Combustion Engineering, fuel gasification, 1977 October 18 (Box 754)
    - Connecticut Region of Hadassah, “Hand of Healing’ Luncheon, 1977 October 20 (Box 754)
    - New England Conference on National Balanced Growth and Economic Development, 1977 October 22 (Box 754)
    - Opening of Central Naugatuck Valley Region Higher Education Center, 1977 October 23 (Box 754)
    - Connecticut Congress on Volunteerism and Citizenship, Meriden, 1977 October 24 (Box 754)
    - International Association Lions Club, New Haven, 1977 October 26 (Box 754)
    - Business Week Reception, 1977 October 27 (Box 754)
    - Catholic Women, San Antonio, 1977 November 3 (Box 754)
    - Putnam Phalanx, 119th Anniversary, 1977 November 5 (Box 754)
    - Waterbury Democratic Rally, 1977 November 6 (Box 754)
    - Johnson Fund Raising, West Haven, 1977 November 8 (Box 755)
    - 3rd Anniversary of Prison Store Opening, 1977 November 9 (Box 755)
    - Connecticut Rail Seminar, North Haven, 1977 November 10 (Box 755)
    - New England Society of Newspaper Editors, Mystic, 1977 November 11 (Box 755)
    - National Conference of Puerto Rican Women Hartford, 1977 November 12 (Box 755)
    - West Haven Rotary Club, 1977 November 16 (Box 755)
    - Lyme/Old Lime, Old Saybrook Chamber of Commerce - Computer Added to Office of Municipal Assistance, 1977 November 16 (Box 755)
    - Dedication of Baggage Facility, Bradley Field, 1977 November 18 (Box 755)
    - Graduation Pratt & Whitney, Employees, High School Equivalency work, 1977 November 18 (Box 755)
    - Annual Dinner Connecticut Business & Industry Associations, 1977 November 22 (Box 755)
    - Budget Hearing, Norwalk, 1977 November 23 (Box 755)
    - Budget Hearing, Canton, 1977 November 29 (Box 755)
    - Budget Hearing, Groton, 1977 November 30 (Box 755)
    - Council of State Governments, Eastern Regional Conference, 1977 December 5 (Box 755)
    - Senior Management Official, Pratt & Whitney, 1977 December 12 (Box 755)
    - State Government Managers, Bushnell, Hartford, 1977 December 14 (Box 755)
    - Youth Conference (in speech file only), 1977 December 15 (Box 755)
    - Budget remarks, Hartford (Urban Action Task Force), 1977 December 15 (Box 755)
    - Statement re I-84, 1977 December 29 (Box 755)
    - Hartford Chamber of Commerce, 1977 December 29 (Box 755)
    - Logue Inauguration, 1978 January 1 (Box 755)
    - Insulation, Materials, Applications, Hazards, Northeast Utilities, Berlin, 1978 January 10 (Box 755)
    - Connecticut Economic Development Corporation, SNETCO, New Haven, 1978 January 12 (Box 755)
    - Marine Club, Man of the Year Award - Killian, 1978 January 12 (Box 755)
    - Installation of Officers, Connecticut Association of Realtors, Hartford, 1978 January 13 (Box 755)
    - Opening Symposium on Unification of the Courts, 1978 January 13 (Box 755)
    - Israeli Friendship Flight Visitors, 1978 January 25 (Box 755)
    - Southern New England Telephone Company 100th Anniversary of Realtors Dinner, 1978 January 27 (Box 755)
    - Beautiful Chamber of Commerce Speech, Waterbury, 1978 January 30 (Box 755)
    - National Jewish Hospital Award, 1978 February 2 (Box 755)
    - George Washington Carver Foundations, 1978 February 10 (Box 755)
    - Budget Speech, 1978 February 10 (Box 755)
    - State Police Awards, 1978 February 17 (Box 755)
    - Connecticut Association Chamber of Commerce Executives, 1978 February 24 (Box 755)
    - Taxpayers Association Annual Meeting, 1978 February 25 (Box 755)
    - Lower Naugatuck Valley Chamber of Commerce, 1978 March 1 (Box 755)
    - Annual Meeting International Reading Association (Delivered by Mark Shedd), 1978 March 2 (Box 755)
    - Intergovernmental Seminar, University of Connecticut Health Center, 1978 March 3 (Box 755)
    - Jefferson, Jackson, Bailey Dinner, 1978 March 4 (Box 755)
    - Dental Hygienists and Assistants, University of Connecticut Health Center, 1978 March 5 (Box 755)
    - Middletown Rotary Club, 1978 March 7 (Box 755)
    - National Honor Society, Derby High, 1978 March 8 (Box 755)
    - Student Intercollegiate Legislature, 1978 March 10 (Box 755)
    - St. Patrick’s Day
    - League of Women Voters Day, 1978 March 29 (Box 755)
    - Coalition on Aging, Legislative Forum, 1978 March 29 (Box 755)
    - Municipal Finance Forum, 1978 March 30 (Box 755)
    - Christian Conference of Connecticut Legislative Seminar, 1978 March 30
    - Hall of Fame Induction Ceremonies, Connecticut High School Coaches Association, 1978 March 31 (Box 755)
    - CETA Youth Program Workshop, 1978 April 4 (Box 755)
    - Housing Conference - Governors Favors Creation of Division of Housing in Department of Economic Development, 1978 April 11 (Box 755)
    - Connecticut Fire Marshals Induction, Hebron, 1978 April 12 (Box 755)
    - RHAM Honor Society Induction, Hebron, 1978 April 12 (Box 755)
    - Women in Leadership, New Haven, 1978 April 13 (Box 755)
    - Opening Connecticut Mental Health Centers, Hispanics Services Division, New Haven, 1978 April 13 (Box 755)
    - New England Regional Conference on Product Safety, Hartford, 1978 April 17 (Box 755)
    - Solar Energy Task Force, National Governors’ Assn., 1978 April 17 (Box 755)
    - Legislative Interns, State Capitol, 1978 April 18 (Box 755)
    - Connecticut Conference on Criminal Victimization of Older Persons, East Hartford, 1978 April 19 (Box 755)
    - American Women in Radio and TV (raised reward to $20,000 in major criminal cases) (in speech file too), 1978 April 20 (Box 755)
    - Middletown Exchange Club, Portland, 1978 April 20 (Box 755)
    - U.S. Association of Evening Students, Enfield, 1978 April 22 (Box 755)
    - Eastern Star, 1978 April 27 (Box 755)
    - Closing the End of the Session, 1978 May 3 (Box 755)
    - Old Guard, West Hartford (Senior Citizens), 1978 May 9 (Box 755)
    - 74th Connecticut Baptist Missionary Convention, 1978 May 12 (Box 755)
    - Connecticut Lions Convention, Grossingers, 1978 May 12 (Box 755)
    - Civil Preparedness Conference for Hispanics, 1978 May 12 (Box 755)
    - Knights of Columbus, Connecticut State Council, Windsor Locks, 1978 May 13 (Box 755)
    - Connecticut’s Public Expenditure Committee, New Haven, 1978 May 16 (Box 755)
    - The Future of the Arts in Connecticut at Wesleyan University, 1978 May 16 (Box 755)
    - Knights of St. Patrick's, 1978 May 17 (Box 755)
    - North Haven Senior Citizens Luncheon, 1978 May 17 (Box 755)
    - Connecticut Association of Health Care Facilities Vernon, 1978 May 17 (Box 755)
    - Awards to Featuring Impaired, 1978 May 18 (Box 755)
    - Thames Valley (?) Grandparents 12th Anniversary Recognition Day, 1978 May 18 (Box 755)
    - Valley Forge Dedication, 1978 May 20 (Box 755)
    - Shakespeare Theater “Arts Night”, 1978 May 20 (Box 755)
    - Main Street, U.S.A New Britain, 1978 May 20 (Box 755)
    - Instructors of the Handicapped Day Manchester High, 1978 May 21 (Box 755)
    - Elizabethan Pageant, Farmington High, 1978 May 21 (Box 755)
    - Brai Birth Man of the Year - Judge Cramer, 1978 May 21 (Box 755)
    - Red Cross Convention, 1978 May 22 (Box 755)
    - Quebec Square Village, Renovation Providing Elderly and Low Modern Income Housing, 1978 May 23 (Box 755)
    - Commencement, Eastern Connecticut State College, Willimantic, 1978 May 23 (Box 755)
    - Dedication of Norwich Armory, 1978 May 23 (Box 755)
    - Senior Consumer day, Bilingual Consumer Alert Program, 1978 May 24 (Box 755)
    - Dedication of the Mentally Retarded Center, 1978 May 31 (Box 755)
    - Catholic Charities Budget, 1978 June 1 (Box 755)
    - Stamford Catholic High School, 1978 June 4 (Box 755)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce sponsored lunch in New York City, 1978 June 7 (Box 755)
    - Conference on Child Abuse, 1978 June 8 (Box 755)
    - New Haven minister's wives, 1978 June 10 (Box 755)
    - Connecticut leadership 78 Conference, Mather Student Center, Hartford, at Trinity, 1978 June 14 (Box 755)
    - Conference on Reality of Rape, New Haven, 1978 June 14 (Box 755)
    - Dinosaur Park Dedication of Dome, Rocky Hill, 1978 June 14 (Box 755)
    - Boy's State, 1978 June 20 (Box 755)
    - Windham Regional Vocational Technical School Graduation, 1978 June 21 (Box 755)
    - Connecticut Junior Republic Commencement, 1978 June 23 (Box 755)
    - Council of Small Towns in Hartford, 1978 June 23 (Box 755)
    - Opening of Veterans Information Center, Hartford, 1978 June 27 (Box 755)
    - Girls’ State, 1978 June 27 (Box 755)
    - Winsted area Rotary Club, 1978 July 10 (Box 755)
    - American Legion Auxiliary convention, 1978 July 13 (Box 755)
    - U.S. Dept. of Energy re Stanby gasoline rationing plan, 1978 August 1 (Box 755)
    - Testimony re President's urban program in D.C., 1978 August 9 (Box 755)
    - Dedication of Danbury Hospital psychiatric unit, 1978 August 14 (Box 755)
    - Police Association of Connecticut in Wallingford, 1978 August 16 (Box 755)
    - First Annual Scholarship Dinner Urban League of Hartford, 1978 August 17 (Box 755)
    - Laurel Hill Educational Complex, Waterbury, 1978 August 20 (Box 755)
    - Conference on Defense Dependency and New England, Hartford, 1978 August 21 (Box 755)
    - Italian-American War Vets, Hartford, 1978 August 25 (Box 755)
    - Avery Park Senior Citizens Housing Project, 1978 August 25 (Box 755)
    - Muscular Dystrophy jamboree by CBers, 1978 August 25 (Box 755)
    - Knights of Columbus Testimonial to Louis Sidoli, 1978 August 26 (Box 755)
    - Testimony submitted to Subcommittee on Newspersons' Rights of the Judiciary Committee, 1978 September 6 (Box 755)
    - Organizational Meeting, new State Housing Coordinating Committee, 1978 September 8 (Box 756)
    - Greater Enfield Chamber of Commerce, 1978 September 18 (Box 756)
    - Visit of Joseph Califano, Secretary of HUD, 1978 September 19 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Safety Commission, 1978 September 19 (Box 756)
    - Eastern States Exposition, 1978 September 20 (Box 756)
    - Conference on Alternative to Sewers, 1978 September 20 (Box 756)
    - Junior Achievement, Western Connecticut, 1978 September 20 (Box 756)
    - Seniors' Consumer Forum, 1978 September 21 (Box 756)
    - Home Builders Association, 1978 September 21 (Box 756)
    - State Firemen's Convention, 1978 September 23 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Agricultural Info Council, 1978 September 25 (Box 756)
    - Hartford County Courthouse 50th Anniversary, 1978 September 25 (Box 756)
    - Rotary Clubs of Stamford, Greenwich, Byram, Cos, Cob, etc., 1978 September 26 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut State Employees Association Annual Convention, 1978 September 28 (Box 756)
    - Small Business International Marketing Conference, 1978 September 28 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut State Employees Association Annual Banquet, 1978 September 30 (Box 756)
    - Democratic Kickoff Dinner, 1978 September 30 (Box 756)
    - Stamford area Commerce & Industry Association, 1978 October 6 (Box 756)
    - Associated Press Circuit & Connecticut Editorial Association, 1978 October 12 (Box 756)
    - Association of Retired Teachers, 1978 October 17 (Box 756)
    - First International Conference on Business Opportunities for Health Care Industries, 1978 October 17 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Council of Senior Citizens, 1978 October 18 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Federation Business and Professional Women's Clubs, 1978 October 21 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Credit Union League, 1978 October 21 (Box 756)
    - 323 Luncheon, United Church, New Haven, 1978 October 23 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Association of Realtors, 1978 October 24 (Box 756)
    - NAACP, 1978 October 28 (Box 756)
    - Seniors' Consumer Forum, Norwalk, 1978 November 2 (Box 756)
    - Work Co-op program initiated by Hamilton Standard Division of United Technologies, 1978 November 21 (Box 756)
    - CBIA annual meeting, 1978 November 21 (Box 756)
    - Urban League of Greater Hartford, 1978 November 28 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Farm Bureau Federation, East Hartford, 1978 November 30 (Box 756)
    - First meeting of the Advisory Council for the State Board of Higher Education, 1978 December 13 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council, 1978 December 13 (Box 756)
    - Windsor Locks Senior Citizens Center, 1978 December 16 (Box 756)
    - Testimony re home heating fuel prices, 1978 December 20 (Box 756)
    - Inaugural Address, 1979 January 3 (Box 756)
    - 12th Annual Pharmacists Licensure Ceremony, Hartford, 1979 January 4 (Box 756)
    - 200th Birthday, Town of Southington, 1979 January 7 (Box 756)
    - Budget hearing, Torrington, 1979 January 9 (Box 756)
    - Budget hearing, Stamford, 1979 January 10 (Box 756)
    - Budget Hearing, Norwich, 1979 January 12 (Box 756)
    - Handicapped Act, 1979 January 12 (Box 756)
    - Youth Action Conference, 1979 January 26 (Box 756)
    - CBIA & Chamber of Commerce Executives Luncheon, 1979 January 26 (Box 756)
    - Midwinter Meeting Connecticut Education Association, 1979 January 27 (Box 756)
    - Industrial Payroll Savings Bond Campaign, 1979 January 31 (Box 756)
    - Briefing of Connecticut Congressional Delegation on President's budget, 1979 February 1 (Box 756)
    - Luncheon honoring Lou Bachman, retiring editor, Bristol Press, 1979 February 2 (Box 756)
    - Budget Message, 1979 February 7 (Box 756)
    - New England Community Action Program, 1979 February 14 (Box 756)
    - Hartford Juvenile Court and Detention Building, 1979 February 20 (Box 756)
    - Hospice speech to National Governors' Association, 1979 February 27 (Box 756)
    - Jefferson, Jackson, Bailey Dinner, 1979 March 3 (Box 756)
    - E. Bartlett Barnes Testimonial, 1979 March 20 (Box 756)
    - Energy hearing, 1979 March 22 (Box 756)
    - Hall of Fame Lunch, 199 March 23 (Box 756)
    - Italian-American Democratic Club of Waterbury, 1979 March 28 (Box 756)
    - Opening of Project Detour, Juvenile Court, Uncasville, 1979 March 30 (Box 756)
    - Atlanta University Training Conference, 1979 April 4 (Box 756)
    - Friars Dinner honoring Senator Joseph Fauliso, 1979 April 20 (Box 756)
    - Holocaust Memorial Observance, Hartford Jewish Community Center, 1979 April 22 (Box 756)
    - Commemoration of the Holocaust, Senate Chambers, 1979 April 23 (Box 756)
    - Northeastern Weights and Measures Association Conference, Hartford, 1979 April 24 (Box 756)
    - Energy Conservation Conference, Hartford, 1979 April 24 (Box 756)
    - Conference on Prevention of Child Abuse, Spousal Abuse, Delinquency, etc., 1979 April 25 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Economic Development Corporation, 1979 April 26 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Development Council Tour for Industrial Realtors, University of Bridgeport, 1979 May 2 (Box 756)
    - Governors' Committee on Fitness, Hartford, 1979 May 12 (Box 756)
    - Dedication of Xerox Corp. Headquarters, Stamford, 1979 May 14 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Economic Development Corporation, Darien, 1979 May 14 (Box 756)
    - Combustion Engineering, Annual Safety Seminar, Hartford, 9179 May 14 (Box 756)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Hartford, 1979 May 15 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council, 1979 Mary 16 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Licensed Practical Nurses Association, 1979 May 16 (Box 756)
    - Transportation Brokerage & Ridesharing Seminar, Hartford, 1979 May 17 (Box 756)
    - Rededication of Old State House, 1979 May 19 (Box 756)
    - Connecticut Alliance of Business, 1979 May 23 (Box 756)
    - Memorial Day services, Capitol Rotunda, 1979 May 24 (Box 756)
    - World Trade Week Dinner, New Haven, 1979 May 24 (Box 756)
    - Western Connecticut State College Commencement, 1979 May 26 (Box 756)
    - Wesleyan University Commencement, 1979 May 27 (Box 756)
    - Close of General Assembly, 1979 June 6 (Box 756)
    - GTE Stamford Employees Good Government Club, 1979 June 13 (Box 756)
    - Municipal Energy Conference at Capitol, 1979 June 15 (Box 756)
    - Boy's State, 1979 June 19 (Box 756)
    - Governor asks town energy coordinators to meet with gas station people for weekend service, 1979 June 21 (Box 756)
    - Report on talk with President on more gas for Connecticut and home heating oil, 1979 July 2 (Box 756)
    - Independence Day, Colebrook, 1979 July 4 (Box 756)
    - First Meeting of State Employment and Training Council, 1979 July 31 (Box 756)
    - Energy Town Meetings on home heating oil, 1979 August 14 (Box 756)
    - Energy Town Meeting, Stamford, 1979 August 20 (Box 756)
    - Energy Town Meeting, Litchfield, 1979 August 28 (Box 756)
    - New England Governors with Secretary of Energy Duncan, Boston, 1979 August 28 (Box 756)
    - Energy Town Meeting, Bloomfield, 1979 August 29 (Box 756)
    - John DiBiaggio's inauguration as President of the University of Connecticut, 1979 September 8 (Box 756)
    - AARP and National Retired Teachers' Association President's visit, 1979 September 12 (Box 757)
    - State Labor Council Annual Convention, New Haven, 1979 September 13 (Box 757)
    - Conference on Civil Preparedness, Bridgeport, 1979 September 13 (Box 757)
    - 10th Anniversary Wheeler Clinic, Plainville, 1979 September 27 (Box 757)
    - Danbury Rotary Club, 1979 October 3 (Box 757)
    - American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials, Hartford, 1979 October 15 (Box 757)
    - Union Station Hartford, 1979 October 15 (Box 757)
    - Eastern Regional Child Support Enforcement Seminar, State Senate, 1979 October 22 (Box 757)
    - Energy Workshop, "Saving Ten Percent More Oil", Bridgeport, 1979 October 25 (Box 757)
    - Introduction of President Jimmy Carter at Energy Summit, Providence, R.I., 1979 October 29 (Box 757)
    - Keynote, energy Summit, Providence, R.I., 1979 October 29 (Box 757)
    - Conference on the Use of Energy in Schools and Colleges, Hartford, 1979 October 31 (Box 757)
    - Opening of Special Session, 1979 October 31 (Box 757)
    - Inauguration of Operation of Fuel Bank Campaign, 1979 November 7 (Box 757)
    - First New England Conference on Tourism, 1979 November 19 (Box 757)
    - Budget hearing, Bridgeport, 1979 November 26 (Box 757)
    - Youth Action Conference, 1979 December 6 (Box 757)
- Restricted, 1972-1979
  - Restricted, 1972-1979 (Box 760)
    Original documents from Boxes 223, 224, 225, 473, and 558 related to Mental Health that contain confidential personal information. Redacted copies have been put in their place.